=I Want to Resign Every Single Day=
= أريد أن أستقيل كل يوم =
=Episode 17=
= الحلقة 17 =
Tell us.
أخبرنا.
Why do you work in my company?
لماذا تعمل في شركتي؟
Chu Zhe. Mr. Chu Tian's son.
تشو زهي ، ابن السيد تشو تيان.
Indeed.
في الواقع.
I'm the successor of Tengfei Group.
أنا خليفة مجموعة Tengfei.
Zhe,
زهي ،
did you really tamper with the elevator
هل حقا عبثت بالمصعد
to kill Jin Shi'an?
لقتل جين شيان؟
What elevator?
ما المصعد؟
This morning, the Maintenance Department
هذا الصباح قسم الصيانة
found this when fixing the elevator.
وجدت هذا عند إصلاح المصعد.
It can black out the elevator with remote control
يمكنه تعتيم المصعد بجهاز التحكم عن بعد
and make it fall.
وجعله يسقط.
You think I put this in the elevator
تعتقد أنني وضعت هذا في المصعد
to kill Mr. Jin?
لقتل السيد جين؟
You've read too many ridiculous novels.
لقد قرأت الكثير من الروايات السخيفة.
It's the 21st century.
إنه القرن الحادي والعشرون.
I'm not a villain for business battles.
أنا لست شريرًا في معارك العمل.
My father indeed sent me
لقد أرسلني والدي بالفعل
to check on the bidding stuff.
للتحقق من الاشياء المزايدة.
But I refused.
لكني رفضت.
I want Tengfei and New Era
أريد Tengfei و New Era
to have fair and healthy competition
للحصول على منافسة عادلة وصحية
and learn from each other
ونتعلم من بعضنا البعض
instead of playing dirty tricks.
بدلا من لعب الحيل القذرة.
Oh, I see.
حسنا أرى ذلك.
Secretary Bai,
سكرتير باي ،
I didn't know you thought of me like this.
لم أكن أعرف أنك فكرت بي هكذا.
If this is why
إذا كان هذا هو السبب
you invited me to dinner,
لقد دعوتني لتناول العشاء ،
I should go.
يجب ان اذهب.
Looks like we misunderstood him.
يبدو أننا أسأنا فهمه.
He seems to be a very simple man.
يبدو أنه رجل بسيط للغاية.
The successor of Tengfei Group works in our company, simple?
يعمل خليفة Tengfei Group في شركتنا ، بسيط؟
You're the simple one, I'm afraid.
أنت الشخص البسيط ، أخشى.
Why do you sound so sarcastic?
لماذا تبدو ساخرا جدا؟
I don't think Chu Zhe is a bad guy.
لا أعتقد أن Chu Zhe رجل سيء.
How many times have you had dinner with him
كم مرة تناولت العشاء معه
and you trust him so much?
وأنت تثق به كثيرا؟
I wanted to have dinner with him.
كنت أرغب في تناول العشاء معه.
But you ruined it every time.
لكنك دمرته في كل مرة.
Are you blaming me?
هل تلومني؟
Don't wander from the subject.
لا تبتعد عن الموضوع.
If Chu Zhe didn't do that,
إذا لم يفعل Chu Zhe ذلك ،
who else could it be?
من آخر يمكن أن يكون؟
The control device was removed.
تمت إزالة جهاز التحكم.
The Maintenance Department didn't tell anyone, did they?
لم تخبر دائرة الصيانة أحدا ، أليس كذلك؟
No. I asked them to keep it secret.
لا ، لقد طلبت منهم إبقاء الأمر سراً.
Good.
جيد.
I've got a risky plan.
لدي خطة محفوفة بالمخاطر.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
(Secretary Bai)
(السكرتير باي)
(Nagger is calling.)
(ناغر يتصل.)
Hello.
مرحبًا.
I'm going into the elevator.
انا ذاهب الى المصعد.
The murderer will do something.
القاتل سيفعل شيئاً.
Watch carefully
راقب بعنايه
and remember all suspicious guys.
وتذكر كل الرجال المشبوهين.
Let's catch him in the next loop.
دعونا نلحق به في الحلقة التالية.
OK. Boss,
نعم.  رئيس،
stay safe.
ابق آمنا.
If I die, I'll see you in the next loop.
إذا مت ، سأراك في الحلقة التالية.
(The ground floor.)
(الطابق الأرضي.)
(The guy didn't fall for it.)
(الرجل لم يقع في غرامها).
(Secretary Bai)
(السكرتير باي)
(Nagger is calling.)
(ناغر يتصل.)
Nagger?
ناجر؟
(Secretary Bai, Nagger)
(السكرتير باي ، ناجر)
Me?
أنا؟
(Nagger is calling.)
(ناغر يتصل.)
Bai Jing!
باي جينغ!
(Unknown number)
(رقم مجهول)
Jin Shi'an,
جين شيان ،
if you want Bai Jing to live,
إذا كنت تريد أن يعيش باي جينغ ،
come immediately to the deserted parking lot.
تعال على الفور إلى موقف السيارات المهجور.
Don't call the police.
لا تتصل بالشرطة.
Hello? Hello!
مرحبًا؟  مرحبًا!
Bai Jing!
باي جينغ!
Don't come any closer! Don't!
لا تقترب أكثر!  لا!
Smart guys. You found the secret of the elevator.
الرجال الأذكياء.  لقد وجدت سر المصعد.
I have to change my plan.
لا بد لي من تغيير خطتي.
What do you want? Money?
ماذا تريد؟  مال؟
I want to kill you.
اريد قتلك.
Who sent you?
من ارسلها لك؟
Don't waste your time.
لا تضيعوا وقتكم.
Don't hurt her!
لا تؤذيها!
Roll the stick to me.
لف العصا لي.
Don't listen to him. Call the police!
لا تستمع إليه.  اتصل بالشرطة!
Shut up.
اسكت.
I said, don't hurt her!
قلت ، لا تؤذيها!
Roll the stick to me.
لف العصا لي.
Do it.
افعلها.
Jin Shi'an!
جين شيآن!
Stop beating him!
توقفوا عن ضربه!
Stop it!
توقف عن ذلك!
Mr. Zhang?
السيد تشانغ؟
Morning, Mr. Zhang.
صباح الخير ، السيد تشانغ.
In Unit 2, Building 1, Xinyue Community,
في الوحدة 2 ، المبنى 1 ، مجتمع Xinyue ،
here's an elevator accident.
هنا حادث مصعد.
Please come immediately.
من فضلك تعال على الفور.
I had planned to kill you alone.
كنت قد خططت لقتلك وحدك.
But now, I'll kill you both.
لكن الآن ، سأقتلكما كلاكما.
(See you in the next loop.)
(نراكم في الحلقة التالية).
Bai Jing!
باي جينغ!
Wake up!
استيقظ!
We are
نحن
now square.
الآن مربع.
=I Want to Resign Every Single Day=
= أريد الاستقالة كل يوم =
(The right of communication through network exclusively belongs to Tencent.)
(يعود حق الاتصال عبر الشبكة حصريًا إلى Tencent.)